bazarlec.com 2016-11-11

# Privacy Policy

THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS A LEGALLY BINDING DOCUMENT BETWEEN YOU AND BAZARLEC (BOTH TERMS DEFINED BELOW). THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL BE EFFECTIVE UPON YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE SAME (DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY IN ELECTRONIC FORM, BY CLICKING ON THE ‘I ACCEPT’ TAB OR BY USE OR THE WEBSITE OR BY OTHER MEANS) AND WILL GOVERN THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN YOU AND BAZARLEC FOR YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE (DEFINED BELOW).

Important Note: This graphic is simulation only. Your actual product graphic/face may vary due to photography. These below mentioned things can be different:

brightness, extra shiny, shade, angle, clarity, edge, color (colour) feel

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU INDICATE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND, AGREE AND CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. YOU HEREBY PROVIDE YOUR UNCONDITIONAL CONSENT OR AGREEMENTS TO BAZARLEC.com AS PROVIDED UNDER SECTION 43A AND SECTION 72A OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000. 

By providing us your Information or by making use of the facilities provided by the Website, You hereby consent to the collection, storage, processing and transfer of any or all of Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information by BaZarlec.com as specified under this Privacy Policy. You further agree that such collection, use, storage and transfer of Your Information shall not cause any loss or wrongful gain to you or any other person.

Smartlec Private Limited and its subsidiaries and affiliates and Associate Companies (individually and/ or collectively, "bazarlec.com") is/are concerned about the privacy of the data and information of users (including sellers and buyers/customers whether registered or non- registered) accessing, offering, selling or purchasing products or services on BaZarlec’s websites, mobile sites or mobile applications ("Website") on the Website and otherwise doing business with BaZarlec. “Associate Companies” here shall have the same meaning as ascribed in Companies Act, 2013. 

The terms “We” / “Us” / “Our” individually and collectively refer to each entity being part of the definition of BaZarlec and the terms "You" / "Your" / "Yourself” refer to the users.   
This Privacy Policy is a contract between you and the respective BaZarlec.com entity whose Website You use or access or you otherwise deal with. This Privacy Policy shall be read together with the respective Terms Of Use or other terms and condition of the respective BaZarlec.com entity and its respective Website or nature of business of the Website. 

 **BaZarlec has provided this Privacy Policy to familiarize you with.**    

The type of data or information that you share with or provide to BaZarlec.com and that BaZarlec.com collects from you; the purpose for collection of such data or information from you is; BaZarlec’s information security practices and policies; and BaZarlec’s policy on sharing or transferring your data or information with third parties.

This Privacy Policy may be amended / updated from time to time. Upon amending / updating the Privacy Policy, we will accordingly amend the date above. We suggest that you regularly check this Privacy Policy to apprise yourself of any updates. Your continued use of Website or provision of data or information thereafter will imply your unconditional acceptance of such updates to this Privacy Policy.

 **1.      ****Why we are collecting and storing such information:** ****

Consist of Type of “Personal Information (in the form of data)” and “Non-Personal Information (in the form of data)” provided by you to BaZarlec.com or Collected from you by BaZarlec.com

 **1.** Personal Information is used to uniquely identification purpose or to reach you. Personal Information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy shall include, but not be limited to: ****

(a) Your address,

(b) Your telephone number,

(c) Your e-mail address or other contact information,

(d) Your date of birth,

(e) Your gender,

(f)  Information regarding your transactions on the Website, (including sales or purchase history),

(g) Your financial information such as bank account information or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details,

(h) Your financial information such as bank account information or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details,

(i)   Internet Protocol address,

(j)   Any other items of ‘sensitive personal data or information’ as such term is defined under the Information Technology 

(k)  Identification code of your communication device which you use to access the Website or otherwise deal with any BaZarlec entity, any other Information that you provide during your registration process, if any, on the Website.

 **Such Personal Information may be collected in various ways including during the course of your presence or absence:**         

a.) Registering as a user on the Website 

b.) Registering as a seller on the Website,

c.) Availing certain services offered on the Website. Such instances include but are not limited to making an offer for sale, online purchase, participating in any online survey or contest, communicating with BaZarlec’s customer service by phone, email or otherwise or posting user reviews on the items available on the Website, or through any medium.

d.) Otherwise doing business on the Website or otherwise dealing with any BaZarlec entity.

We may receive Personal information about you from third parties, such as social media services, commercially available sources and business partners. If you access Website through a social media service or connect a service on Website to a social media service, the information we collect may include your user name associated with that social media service, any information or content the social media service has the right to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends list, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Website or otherwise deal with any BaZarlec entity through social media services or when you connect any Website to social media services, you are authorizing BaZarlec to collect, store, and use and retain such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

1.2 **Non-Personal Information**

BaZarlec may also collect information other than Personal Information from you through the Website when you visit and/or use the Website. Such information may be stored in server logs. This Non-Personal Information would not assist BaZarlec to identify you personally.

 **This Non-Personal Information may include:**.                    

        a.   Your geographic location,

                b.    Details of Your telecom service provider or internet service provider,

c.   The type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome etc.),

        d.   The operating system of your system, device and the Website You last visited before visiting the Website,

e.   The duration of your stay on the Website is also stored in the session along with the date and time of your access,

Non-Personal Information is collected through various ways such through the use of cookies. BaZarlec.com may store temporary or permanent ‘cookies’ on your computer. You can erase or choose to block these cookies from your computer. You can configure your computer’s browser to alert You when we attempt to send You a cookie with an option to accept or refuse the cookie. If you have turned cookies off, you may be prevented from using certain features of the Website.

Ads: BaZarlec.com may use third-party service providers to serve ads on BaZarlec’s behalf across the internet and sometimes on the Website. They may collect Non- Personal Information about Your visits to the Website, and Your interaction with our products and services on the Website.

Please do note that Personal Information and Non Personal Information may be treated differently as per this Privacy Policy.

 **You hereby represent to BaZarlec.com that**

I). The Information you provide to BaZarlec.com from time to time is and shall be authentic, correct, current and updated and you have all the rights, permissions and consents as may be required to provide such Information to BaZarlec.com

II). You’re providing the Information to BaZarlec and BaZarlec’s consequent storage, collection, usage, transfer, access or processing of the same shall not be in violation of any third party agreement, laws, charter documents, judgments, orders and decrees.

BaZarlec.com and each of BaZarlec entities officers, directors, contractors or agents shall not be responsible for the authenticity of the Information that you or any other user provide to BaZarlec.com You shall ensure and hold harmless BaZarlec and each of BaZarlec entities officers, directors, contracts or agents and any third party relying on the Information provided by You in the event You are in breach of this Privacy Policy including this provision and the immediately preceding provision above.

Your Information will primarily be stored in electronic form however certain data can also be stored in physical form. We may store, collect, process and use your data in countries other than Republic of India but under compliance with applicable laws. We may enter into agreements with third parties (in or outside of India) to store or process your information or data. These third parties may have their own security standards to safeguard your information or data and we will on commercial reasonable basis require from such third parties to adopt reasonable security standards to safeguard your information / data.

 _Smartlec Private Limited_

 _ _All Rights Reserved__
